Bruce Jackson and Diane Christian collection
American Folklife Center, Library of Congress
- Series 2: Sound Recordings
  - Sub-subseries 2: Newport Folk Festival, 1964, July 23-26, 1964
    - 164 / 64 4A / NFF reel 23B - Sunday afternoon concert, July 26, 1964, AFC 2011/009: SR0164; 1 sound tape reel: analog; 7 in.
      - You're Gonna Need Somebody on Your Bond - Buffy Sainte-Marie
    - 165 / 64 4A / NFF reel 24A - Sunday afternoon concert, July 26, 1964, AFC 2011/009: SR0165; 1 sound tape reel: analog; 7 in.
      - Fair and Tender Girls [Come All Ye Fair and Tender Ladies] - Buffy Sainte-Marie
      - Cripple Creek - Buffy Sainte-Marie
      - Codine [Cod'ine] - Buffy Sainte-Marie
      - Universal Soldier - Buffy Sainte-Marie
      - Rag Mama - Kweskin Jug Band
    - 166 / 64 4A / NFF reel - Sunday afternoon concert / Kweskin Jug Band, July 26, 1964, AFC 2011/009: SR0166; 1 sound tape reel: analog; 7 in.
      All songs on this tape performed by the Kweskin Jug Band.
      - Jug Band Music
      - Sadie Green
      - My Gal
      - Ukelele Lady
    - 167 / 64 4E / NFF reel 25A - Sunday evening concert, July 26, 1964, AFC 2011/009: SR0167; 1 sound tape reel: analog; 7 in.
      - Hard Times - Stanley Brothers
      - Man of Constant Sorrow - Stanley Brothers
      - How Far Is It to Little Rock - Stanley Brothers
      - Bury Me Beneath the Willow - Ken and Neriah Benfield
      - [unidentified] - Ken and Neriah Benfield
        Carter family number
      - Blessed Jesus - Ken and Neriah Benfield
      - [unidentified] - Ken and Neriah Benfield
      - Wildwood Flower - Ken and Neriah Benfield
    - 168 / 64 4E / NFF reel 25B - Sunday evening concert, July 26, 1964, AFC 2011/009: SR0168; 1 sound tape reel: analog; 7 in.
      - 22-20 Blues - Skip James (piano)
      - Sick Bed Blues - Skip James (guitar)
      - Cherry Ball Blues - Skip James
      - Roddy McCorley - Clancy Brothers
      - Irish Rover - Clancy Brothers
      - Will You Go, Lassie, Go [probably Wild Mountain Thyme] - Clancy Brothers
    - 169 / 64 4E / NFF reel 26A - Sunday evening concert, July 26, 1964, AFC 2011/009: SR0169; 1 sound tape reel: analog; 7 in.
      - Banks of the Royal Coast - Clancy Brothers
      - Finnegan's Wake - Clancy Brothers
      - Port Lorig - when the Saints [Port Lairge or Port Láirge] - Clancy Brothers
      - Hava Nagila - Clancy Brothers
      - 500 Miles from Home - Hedy West
      - Joe Bowers - Hedy West
      - The Brown Girl - Hedy West
    - 170 / 64 3E / NFF reel 26B - Sunday evening concert, July 26, 1964, AFC 2011/009: SR0170; 1 sound tape reel: analog; 7 in.
      - Anger in the Land - Hedy West
      - Hammer and Nails - Staple Singers
      - Will the Circle Be Unbroken - Staple Singers
      - Don't Drive Me Away - Staple Singers
      - Help Me, Jesus - Staple Singers
      - Pray On, My Child - Staple Singers
    - 171 / 64 4E / NFF reel 27A - Sunday evening concert, July 26, 1964, AFC 2011/009: SR0171; 1 sound tape reel: analog; 7 in.
      - Pray On My Child - Staple Singers
      - Deep Blue Sea - Pete Seeger
      - An Old Man Came Courting
      - Old Joe Clark/Had I a Golden Thread (medley) - Pete Seeger
      - Mamma [?] - Pete Seeger
    - 172 / 64 4E / NFF reel 27B - Sunday evening concert, July 26, 1964, AFC 2011/009: SR0172; 1 sound tape reel: analog; 7 in.
      - Oh Mary Don't You Weep - Pete Seeger
      - Where Have All the Flowers Gone - Pete Seeger
      - The Holy Ground - Pete Seeger
      - Fire on the Mountain - Kentucky Colonels
      - If You're Ever Gonna Love Me - Kentucky Colonels
      - Bill Cheatham - Kentucky Colonels
    - 173 / 64 4E / NFF reel 28A - Sunday evening concert, July 26, 1964, AFC 2011/009: SR0173; 1 sound tape reel: analog; 7 in.
      - If You’re Ever Gonna Love Me - Kentucky Colonels
      - Bill Cheatham - Kentucky Colonels
      - Ain't Gonna Rain No More - Kentucky Colonels
      - Soldier's Joy - Kentucky Colonels
      - Shady Grove - Kentucky Colonels
      - Bye and Bye Will See Jesus - Mississippi John Hurt
      - Sliding Delta - Mississippi John Hurt
    - 174 / 64 4E / NFF 28B - Sunday evening concert, July 26, 1964, AFC 2011/009: SR0174; 1 sound tape reel: analog; 7 in.
      - Talking Casey - Mississippi John Hurt
      - Coffee Blues (Loving Spoonful) - Mississippi John Hurt
      - 99 1/2 Won't Do - Freedom Singers
      - Poor Pilgrim of Sorrow - Freedom Singers
      - Over My Head - Freedom Singers
      - Ain't Gonna Let Nobody - Freedom Singers
      - This Little Light of Mine - Freedom Singers
    - 175 / 64 4E / NFF reel 29A - Sunday evening concert, July 26, 1964, AFC 2011/009: SR0175; 1 sound tape reel: analog; 7 in.
      - This Little Light of Mine - Freedom Singers
      - That's All Right - Freedom Singers and Guy Carawan
      - I've Got a Job - Freedom Singers and Guy Carawan
      - All I Want to Do - Bob Dylan
      - To Ramona - Bob Dylan
    - 176 / 64 4E / NFF reel 29B - Sunday evening concert, July 26, 1964, AFC 2011/009: SR0176; 1 sound tape reel: analog; 7 in.
      - Mr. Tambourine Man - Bob Dylan
      - Chimes of Freedom - Bob Dylan
      - With God on Our Side - Bob Dylan and Joan Baez
    - 177 / 64 4E / NFF reel 30A - Sunday evening concert, July 26, 1964, AFC 2011/009: SR0177; 1 sound tape reel: analog; 7 in.
      - Shake That Thing - Dave Van Ronk Jug Band
      - Maple Leaf Rag - Dave Van Ronk Jug Band
        Written by Scott Joplin
      - Got Another Sweetie Now - Dave Van Ronk Jug Band
      - Alabama Song - Dave Van Ronk Jug Band
      - Can't Keep From Cryin' - Odetta
    - 178 / 64 4E / NFF reel 30B - Sunday evening concert, July 26, 1964, AFC 2011/009: SR0178; 1 sound tape reel: analog; 7 in.
      All songs on this recording performed by Odetta.
      - Troubled
      - My Boy
      - Froggie
      - Long Time Man Feel Bad
      - Look Yonder Black Betty
      - Ain't No Grave
      - My Mind on Freedom
    - 179 / 64 4E / NFF reel 31 / Odetta and finale, July 26, 1964, AFC 2011/009: SR0179; 1 sound tape reel: analog; 7 in.
      - My Mind on Freedom
      - We Shall Overcome
  - Sub-subseries 3: Newport Folk Festival, 1965
    For the 1965 Newport recordings, the number in the ID following "65" is the reel number. Titles for the first four songs by the Cape Breton Singers are very faint.
    - 180 / 65 11, July 23, 1965, AFC 2011/009: SR0180; 1 sound tape reel: analog, 7 1/2 ips, stereo; 7 in.
      - Richland Woman - Mississippi John Hurt
      - Coffee Blues - Mississippi John Hurt
      - [three songs] - Cape Breton Singers
      - Ain faith [?] - Cape Breton Singers
      - Mouth Music: Nead na Circe Fraoich [Nest of the Heather Hen?] - Cape Breton Singers
      - Mouth Music - Cape Breton Singers (Calum)
      - 23rd Psalm - Cape Breton Singers
    - 182 / 65 13, July 23, 1965, AFC 2011/009: SR0181; 1 sound tape reel: analog, 7 1/2 ips, stereo; 7 in.
      - The First Time Ever I Saw Your Face - Peter, Paul and Mary
      - Drop 'em Down Easy - Texas Worksong Group
    - 183 / 65 14 - Evening, stage (continued), July 23, 1965, AFC 2011/009: SR0182; 1 sound tape reel: analog, 7 1/2 ips, stereo; 7 in.
      - Down in Old Ramsey - Texas Worksong Group
      - [?] - Moving Star Hall Singers
        End of Moving Star Hall Singers
    - 184 / 65 15 - Evening, stage (continued), July 23, 1965, AFC 2011/009: SR0183; 1 sound tape reel: analog, 7 1/2 ips, stereo; 7 in.
      Ed Young is the name on the tape box; this is Ed Young and Southern Fife and Drum Corps.
      - Elder Bordee - Larry Older [Lawrence Older]
      - Worried Man Blues - Pete Seeger
      - Dink's Song - Pete Seeger
      - Buy You a Chevrolet - Ed Young
      - Sitting on Top of the World - Ed Young
      - Oree - Ed Young
    - 185 / 65 16 - Evening, stage (continued) / Pete Seeger, July 23, 1965, AFC 2011/009: SR0184; 1 sound tape reel: analog, 7 1/2 ips, stereo; 7 in.
      All songs on this recording performed by Pete Seeger.
      - Coal Creek March
      - Sailing Down My Dirty Stream
      - Go Down, Old Hannah
      - O Mary, Don't You Weep
      - This Land Is Your Land
        End of the July 23 evening stage concert.
    - 186 / 65 17 - Festival field, July 24, 1965, AFC 2011/009: SR0185; 1 sound tape reel: analog, 7 1/2 ips, stereo; 7 in.
      - [possibly six unidentified songs] - Oscar Brand
      - Parties Make the World Go Round - Oscar Brand
        This song is numbered "7" on the tape box
    - 187 / 65 18, July 24, 1965, AFC 2011/009: SR0186; 1 sound tape reel: analog, 7 1/2 ips, stereo; 7 in.
      - [unidentified songs] - Lightning Hopkins
      - Her Mantle So Green - Margaret Barry
    - 188 / 65 19 - Festival field, July 24, 1965, AFC 2011/009: SR0187; 1 sound tape reel: analog, 7 1/2 ips, stereo; 7 in.
      - The Leprechaun - Margaret Barry
    - 189 / 65 20, July 24, 1965, AFC 2011/009: SR0188; 1 sound tape reel: analog, 7 1/2 ips, stereo; 7 in.
      - [three unidentified songs] - Jim Kweskin Jug Band
      - Never Swat A Fly
      - Woke Up This Morning With My Mind Set on Freedom - Odetta
      - Intermission
    - 190 / 65 21, July 24, 1965, AFC 2011/009: SR0189; 1 sound tape reel: analog, 7 1/2 ips, stereo; 7 in.
      - [unidentified song(s)] - John MacFadyen
        Bagpipes
      - Pretty Sally - Aerton [Ayrton?] Barrer
    - 191 / 65 22 - Festival field, July 24, 1965, AFC 2011/009: SR0190; 1 sound tape reel: analog, 7 1/2 ips, stereo; 7 in.
      - Devlish Mary - Aerton [Ayrton?] Barrer
      - Song for Canada - Ian and Sylvia
    - 192 / 65 23, July 24, 1965, AFC 2011/009: SR0191; 1 sound tape reel: analog, 7 1/2 ips, stereo; 7 in.
      - [unidentified song(s)] - Spokes Mashiyane
        Pennywhistle
      - Mother Behan - Theo Bikel
    - 193 / 65 24, July 24-25, 1965, AFC 2011/009: SR0192; 1 sound tape reel: analog, 7 1/2 ips, stereo; 7 in.
      End of July 24 concert plus July 25 afternoon concert
      - [unidentified songs] - Theo Bikel
      - Bimini - Theo Bikel
    - 194 / 65 25 - Afternoon Stage, July 25, 1965, AFC 2011/009: SR0193; 1 sound tape reel: analog, 7 1/2 ips, stereo; 7 in.
      - The Mississippi Sawyer - Byron and Lue Berline
      - George Collins - Kathy and Carol
        Kathy Larisch and Carol McComb
    - 195 / 65 26 / Afternoon Stage, July 25, 1965, AFC 2011/009: SR0194; 1 sound tape reel: analog, 7 1/2 ips, stereo; 7 in.
      - Little Sir Hugh - Kathy and Carol
      - There's A Few - Chambers Brothers
    - 196 / 65 27 - Afternoon Stage, July 25, 1965, AFC 2011/009: SR0195; 1 sound tape reel: analog, 7 1/2 ips, stereo; 7 in.
      - Just A Closer Walk With Thee - Chambers Brothers with Joan Baez
      - Long River - Gordon Lightfoot
    - 197 / 65 28 - Afternoon Stage [field], July 25, 1965, AFC 2011/009: SR0196; 1 sound tape reel: analog, 7 1/2 ips, stereo; 7 in.
      - The Echoes of Heroes - Gordon Lightfoot
      - One Way Ticket - Mimi and Dick Farina [Richard and Mimi Fariña]
    - 198 / 65 29 - Afternoon - Field, July 25, 1965, AFC 2011/009: SR0197; 1 sound tape reel: analog, 7 1/2 ips, stereo; 7 in.
      - Pack Up Your Sorrows - Mimi and Dick Farina [Richard and Mimi Fariña]
    - 199 / 65 30, July 25, 1965, AFC 2011/009: SR0198; 1 sound tape reel: analog, 7 1/2 ips, stereo; 7 in.
      - The Dixie Dew Drop - Charles River Valley Boys
      - Introduction to Mance Lipscomb by Pete Seeger
    - 200 / 65 31, July 25, 1965, AFC 2011/009: SR0199; 1 sound tape reel: analog, 7 1/2 ips, stereo; 7 in.
      - [one unidentified song or more] - Mance Lipscomb
      - Out on the Rolling Sea - Eric Von Schmidt
    - 201 / 65 32, July 25, 1965, AFC 2011/009: SR0200; 1 sound tape reel: analog, 7 1/2 ips, stereo; 7 in.
      - Introduction to the Beers Family - Theo Bikel
      - Long Gone - Cousin Emmy
        Cynthia May Carver
    - 202 / 65 33, July 25, 1965, AFC 2011/009: SR0201; 1 sound tape reel: analog, 7 1/2 ips, stereo; 7 in.
      - Turkey in the Straw - Cousin Emmy
      - Maggie's Farm - Bob Dylan
      - Baby Blue It's All Over Now, Baby Blue] - Bob Dylan
    - 203 / 65 34, July 25, 1965, AFC 2011/009: SR0202; 1 sound tape reel: analog, 7 1/2 ips, stereo; 7 in.
      Only the Dylan song title is documented on the tape box.
      - Mr. Tambourine Man - Bob Dylan
      - [unidentified] - Georgia Sea Island Singers
      - [unidentified] - Moving Star Hall Singers
      - Intermission and end of reel #24
    - 204 / 65 35, July 25, 1965, AFC 2011/009: SR0203; 1 sound tape reel: analog, 7 1/2 ips, stereo; 7 in.
      - Introduction to Ishangi Dance Troupe - Theo Bikel
      - The Murder on the Roads in Alabama [The Murder on the Roads of Alabama] - Len Chandler
    - 205 / 65 36, July 25, 1965, AFC 2011/009: SR0204; 1 sound tape reel: analog, 7 1/2 ips, stereo; 7 in.
      - To Be A Man - Len Chandler
        Reel #25
      - Jolly, Jolly, Jolly - Josh White
        Reel #26.
    - 206 / 65 37, July 25, 1965, AFC 2011/009: SR0205; 1 sound tape reel: analog, 7 1/2 ips, stereo; 7 in.
      - Ballad of Sam Hall - Josh White
      - This Little Light of Mine - Fannie Lou Hamer
        Reel #27
    - 207 / 65 38, July 25, 1965, AFC 2011/009: SR0206; 1 sound tape reel: analog, 7 1/2 ips, stereo; 7 in.
      - Go Tell It on a Mountain - Fannie Lou Hamer
      - Come and Go With Me to That Land - Peter, Paul and Mary
        Reel #28
    - 208 / 65 39, possibly July 22, 1965, AFC 2011/009: SR0207; 1 sound tape reel: analog, 7 1/2 ips, stereo; 7 in.
      - Te Manha - Joan Baez
        To the end of reel #28
      - Rock of Ages (harmonica) - Joan Baez
    - 209 / 65 Blues 1 / 1965 NFF 12, July 23, 1965, AFC 2011/009: SR0208; 1 sound tape reel: analog, 7 1/2 ips, stereo; 7 in.
      - Hey Johnny Take a One on Me - Mance Lipscomb
    - 210 / 65 Blues 2 / 1965 NFF 11, July 23, 1965, AFC 2011/009: SR0209; 1 sound tape reel: analog, 7 1/2 ips, stereo; 7 in.
      - Empire State Express - Son House
      - Stop Time - Mance Lipscomb
    - 211 / 65 Blues 3 / 1965 NFF 10, July 23, 1965, AFC 2011/009: SR0210; 1 sound tape reel: analog, 7 1/2 ips, stereo; 7 in.
      - [unidentified] - Mississippi John Hurt
      - Death Letter Blues - Son House
    - 212 / 65 Blues 4 / 1965 NFF 9, July 23, 1965, AFC 2011/009: SR0211; 1 sound tape reel: analog, 7 1/2 ips, stereo; 7 in.
      - Lovin' Spoonful - Rev. Gary Davis
      - Introduction to Mississippi John Hurt - Rev. Gary Davis
    - 213 / 65 Blues 5 / 1965 NFF 8, July 23, 1965, AFC 2011/009: SR0212; 1 sound tape reel: analog, 7 1/2 ips, stereo; 7 in.
      - Wrinkles - Dixon and Leake
        Willie Dixon and Lafayette Leake
      - Why Don't You All Quit It - Paul Butterfield
    - 214 / 65 Blues 6 / 1965 NFF 7, July 23, 1965, AFC 2011/009: SR0213; 1 sound tape reel: analog, 7 1/2 ips, stereo; 7 in.
      - Wayfaring Stranger - Bill Monroe and his Blue Grass Boys
      - Long Lost Child - Willie Dixon and Leake
    - 215 / 65 Blues 7 / 1965 NFF 6, July 23, 1965, AFC 2011/009: SR0214; 1 sound tape reel: analog, 7 1/2 ips, stereo; 7 in.
      - Angel Child - Son House and Mance Lipscomb
      - House of David Blues - Sam and Kirk McGee
    - 216 / 65 Blues 8 / 1965 NFF 5, July 23, 1965, AFC 2011/009: SR0215; 1 sound tape reel: analog, 7 1/2 ips, stereo; 7 in.
      - [unknown number of songs] - Ed Young Fife and Drum Corps
        Ed Young and Southern Fife and Drum Corps
      - Levee Camp Moan - Son House and Mance Lipscomb
    - 217 / 65 Blues 9 / 1965 NFF 4, July 23, 1965, AFC 2011/009: SR0216; 1 sound tape reel: analog, 7 1/2 ips, stereo; 7 in.
      - Make Me a Pallet [Make Me a Pallet on the Floor] - Mississippi John Hurt
      - Special Rider - Skip James
        "End of #3"
    - 218 / 65 Blues 10 / 1965 NFF 3, July 23, 1965, AFC 2011/009: SR0217; 1 sound tape reel: analog, 7 1/2 ips, stereo; 7 in.
      - [unidentified] - Lightning Hopkins
      - Hop Joint - Mississippi John Hurt
    - 219 / 65 Blues 11 / 1965 NFF 2, July 23, 1965, AFC 2011/009: SR0218; 1 sound tape reel: analog, 7 1/2 ips, stereo; 7 in.
      - Empire State Express - Son House
    - 220 / 65 Blues 12 / 1965 NFF 1, July 23, 1965, AFC 2011/009: SR0219; 1 sound tape reel: analog, 7 1/2 ips, stereo; 7 in.
      - Soldier's Drill - Rev. Gary Davis
    - 221 / 65 Blues 13 / 1965 NFF 13, July 23 or 24, 1965, AFC 2011/009: SR0220; 1 sound tape reel: analog, 7 1/2 ips, stereo; 7 in.
      - [?] - Skip James
      - Light Rain - Erik Von Schmidt [Eric Von Schmidt]
    - 222 / 65 Blues 14 / 1965 NFF 14, July 24, 1965, AFC 2011/009: SR0221; 1 sound tape reel: analog, 7 1/2 ips, stereo; 7 in.
      - [unidentified] - Geoff Muldaur and Jim Kweskin
      - Eugene C. from Tennessee - John Koerner [Spider John Koerner]
    - 223 / 65 Blues 15 / 1965 NFF 15, July 24, 1965, AFC 2011/009: SR0222; 1 sound tape reel: analog, 7 1/2 ips, stereo; 7 in.
      - My Love Comes Rolling Down - Erik Von Schmidt, Geoff Muldaur, Mel Lyman
      - River - Jim Kweskin and Mel Lyman
    - 224 / 65 Blues 16 / 1965 NFF 16, July 24, 1965, AFC 2011/009: SR0223; 1 sound tape reel: analog, 7 1/2 ips, stereo; 7 in.
      - Elvira [?] Blues - Paul Butterfield Band
      - Buck #2 - Mance Lipscomb
    - 225 / 65 Blues 17 / 1965 NFF 17, July 23 or 24, 1965, AFC 2011/009: SR0224; 1 sound tape reel: analog, 7 1/2 ips, stereo; 7 in.
      - Ed Young Southern Fife and Drum Corps
      - Chevy - Ed Young and Southern Fife and Drum Corps
      - Oree - Ed Young and Southern Fife and Drum Corps
        End of blues [workshop]
    - 351 / 1180 / Newport 1965-1, July 22, 1965, AFC 2011/009: SR0843; 1 sound tape reel: analog, 7 1/2 ips, 2 track, mono; 7 in.
      According to the manuscript log, Side 1 is a recording of a Texas worksong group brought up by Mac McCormick, comprised of Alfred Paul East, Andrew B. Crane, Charley Colman, Lee Protho, and R.G. Williams.
      - Side 1
      - 1. Fragment
      - 2. I Need Another Witness - R.G. Williams, lead; tree falls
      - 3. Drop 'Em Down Easy - R.G. Williams, lead; chopping trunk into sections
      - 4. Norah - Protho and Crane, then Williams off mic; chopping trunk into sections
      - 5. Hannah [possibly Ol' Hannah] - crane, lead; no working
      - 6. Down On That Old Ramsey Station Farms - Crane, lead; no working
        An adaptation of the song "Cotton Fields."
      - Side 2
        Mance Lipscomb, recorded outside under a tree at Nethercliffe House. Continued on SR0844.
      - 1. Moore Brothers
      - 2. Talk on the song, the brothers, etc.
      - 3. Guitar bits
      - 4. Trouble In Mind
    - 352 / 1181 / Newport 1965-2, July 22-23, 1965, AFC 2011/009: SR0844; 1 sound tape reel: analog, 7 1/2 ips, 2 track, mono; 5 in.
      - Side 1
        Continued from SR0843, Side 2.
      - 1. Welcome Table - Mance Lipscomb (guitar), Fannie Lou Hamer (vocal)
      - 2. This Little Light of Mine - Lipscomb (guitar and vocal), Hamer (vocal), Jean Ritchie (in the background), and Protho
      - 3. Motherless Children - Lipscomb and Hamer
      - 4. When the Saints Go Marching In - Mance, Hamer, Ritchie, and Protho
      - 5. Oh My Lord What Shall I Do - Lipscomb, others
      - 6. I Ain't Got Nobody - Lipscomb
      - 7. Ishangi Singing Style Workshop - Ishangi Dance Troupe, July 23, 1965
      - Side 2
        Considerable blast on this whole side.
      - 1. Ishangi Dance Troupe
      - 2. John Henry - Williams, lead
        His nickname is "40," in reference to his prison sentence.
      - 3. Grizzley Bear - Williams (?), lead; double-cutting
      - 4. Drop 'Em Down Easy - Williams, lead; axes on a log
      - 5. Hannah [possibly Ol' Hannah] - Williams, lead
    - 353 / 1182 / Newport 1965-3 - Group Singing workshop, July 23, 1965, AFC 2011/009: SR0845; 1 sound tape reel: analog, 7 1/2 ips, mono; 5 in.
      - 1. Wool working - Cape Breton Singers
      - 2. Talk about it with Lomax
      - 3. Stewball - East, lead; axes
      - 4. Choppin' Charlie - Lee Protho, lead; hoes
      - 5. Jack O Diamonds (Hammer Ring)
      - 6. Ramsey State Farm - Protho, lead
      - Side 2
      - 1. Little Boy - Lee Protho, then East, Williams; shifting lead
        At blues workshop
      - 2. [two cuts; not completely audible]
      - 3. Talk with East before Crane sings his song
      - 4. My Home - Crane, backed by Williams and Colman
        Recorded in the back yard of the Nethercliffe house
      - 5. Williams talks about he wrote the song "Grizzley Bear"
      - 6. L & N
    - 326 / 65 A1 / International Songs I, 1965, AFC 2011/009: SR0326; 1 sound tape reel: analog; 7 in.
      Information about SR326 appears on the tape box front for SR0327.
      - Theo Bikel
      - A.L. Lloyd
    - 327 / 65 A2 / International Songs II, 1965, AFC 2011/009: SR0327; 1 sound tape reel: analog; 7 in.
      Information about SR327 appears on the tape box front for SR0328.
      - Margaret Barry and Michael Gorman
      - Cape Breton Islanders [Cape Breton Singers]
      - Norman Kennedy
    - 328 / 65 A3 / International Songs III, 1965, AFC 2011/009: SR0328; 1 sound tape reel: analog; 7 in.
      Information about SR328 appears on the tape box front for SR0329.
      - Norman Kennedy
      - Ishangi Dancers [Ishangi Dance Troupe]
      - [?] Band
    - 329 / 65 A4 / International Songs IV, 1965, AFC 2011/009: SR0329; 1 sound tape reel: analog; 7 in.
      Information about SR329 appears on the tape box front for SR0330.
      - Theo Bikel
      - Sasha Zelkin (not a NPFF performer but [a] friend of Theo Bikel)
    - 330 / 65 A5 / International Songs V, 1965, AFC 2011/009: SR0330; 1 sound tape reel: analog; 7 in.
      Information about SR330 appears on the tape box front for SR0326.
      - Ronnie Gilbert
      - Theo Bikel
    - 331 / 65 A6 / String band workshop I, July 23, 1965, AFC 2011/009: SR0331; 1 sound tape reel: analog; 7 in.
      Note written on the tape box back: "had to change machines midway / P. Sigal [?]"
      - Eric Robertson
      - NLCR [New Lost City Ramblers]
      - McGhees
      - Cajuns
    - 332 / 65 A7 / String Band workshop II / P. Sigal, July 23, 1965, AFC 2011/009: SR0332; 1 sound tape reel: analog; 7 in.
      - McGhees
      - Kweskin [probably Jim Kweskin]
      - NLCR [New Lost City Ramblers]
      - Cousin Emmy
    - 333 / 65 A8 / String Band workshop III, July 23, 1965, AFC 2011/009: SR0333; 1 sound tape reel: analog; 7 in.
      - Cousin Emmy
      - McGhees
      - Lillys [Lilly Brothers]
      - Maybelle [Maybelle Carter]
      - Monroe [Bill Monroe, possibly with his Blue Grass Boys]
    - 334 / 65 A9 / String Band workshop IV / Group Singing I, July 23, 1965, AFC 2011/009: SR0334; 1 sound tape reel: analog; 7 in.
      - String Band workshop IV
      - Monroe [Bill Monroe, possibly with his Blue Grass Boys]
      - Group Singing I; C.M. Faurot [possibly the MC]
      - Cape Breton Singers
      - Jean Ritchie
    - 335 / 65 A10 / Group Singing II [Group Songs II on the tape box back], July 23, 1965, AFC 2011/009: SR0335; 1 sound tape reel: analog; 7 in.
      - Texas Workgroup
      - B. Reagan [Bernice Johnson Reagon]
      - Fannie Lou Hamer
      - Len Chandler
      - Pete Seeger
      - Faurot - Chic[?]
    - 336 / 65 A11 / Group Singing III [Group Songs III on the tape box back], July 23, 1965, AFC 2011/009: SR0336; 1 sound tape reel: analog; 7 in.
      - Pete Seeger
      - A.L. Lloyd
    - 337 / 65 A12 / Group Singing IV [Group Songs IV on the tape box back], July 23, 1965, AFC 2011/009: SR0337; 1 sound tape reel: analog; 7 in.
      - Moving Star Hall Singers
    - 338 / 65 A13 / Negro Group Singing I [Negro Group Singing and Rhythmic Patterns on the tape box front], July 23, 1965, AFC 2011/009: SR0338; 1 sound tape reel: analog; 7 in.
      - Ishangi African Dancers [Ishangi Dance Troupe]
    - 339 / 65 A14 / Negro Group Singing II [Negro Group Singing and Rhythmic Patterns on the tape box front], July 23, 1965, AFC 2011/009: SR0339; 1 sound tape reel: analog; 7 in.
      - Moving Star Hall Singers